aerosoles.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Aerosoles

Thank you for visiting the Aerosoles website. Below is our policy to help ensure the privacy of your personally identifiable information. If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the content and practices of our web site, please feel free to contact Aerosoles directly at:

Aerosoles   
Direct Division   
P.O. Box 1916   
Edison, NJ 08818-1916   
Email: Customer Service   
Tel: [800-798-9478](tel:1-800-798-9478) (within the US & Canada) or [732-645-4450](tel:732-645-4450) (outside the US)   
Fax: 732-985-3697

At Aerosoles your privacy is a priority.

At Aerosoles we seek to provide products, services, and offers of value to you and your family. We use information from our interactions with you and other customers, and from other parties, to help us achieve that goal. 

We also recognize and respect your concerns about security and privacy. Accordingly, we have procedures intended to help ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner. 

The Information We Collect

When you visit our website our web server automatically collects information, such as; the domain name (IP address) of the web server that initiated your visit, the referring URL and information about your visit on our site. We also collect and aggregate non-personally identifiable, statistical information, including; the number of visitors to our site, advertising results, survey results, site performance, pages and products viewed, products purchased and how our site was accessed or used. 

Whenever you shop in our stores, through our catalogs, or at Aerosoles.com, you provide us with personal information that we need to complete your transaction or provide the services you request. This information may include your name, address, telephone number, driver’s license number, and email address and the products you purchased. If you use a credit or debit card or pay by check, it will include your account number. 

We also collect information from you when you register or update your account, sign up to receive our emails, request a catalog, or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. This information may include your name, address, phone number, email address and shopping preferences. If you choose to participate in one of our various promotions, contests, programs, or surveys, we may collect additional information from you. For example, if you participate in a survey from us you may provide us with your age, gender, and product or shopping preferences.

Using the Information We Collect

We use the information we collect internally for various purposes, including: to complete your purchase transactions; to provide the services you request; to send you our catalogs and other offerings through the mail or via email; to contact you about the status of your order; to identify your product and service preferences so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you; and to analyze and improve our merchandise selections, services, promotions, website content, customer service, and overall customer shopping experience.

Our Mailing List

Occasionally we make our postal mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products or services may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such mailings, or if you decide that you would no longer like to receive the Aerosoles catalog, just contact us. Please note: we do NOT share email addresses or telephone numbers for any third-party offers.

Our Use of Cookies and Pixel Tags

Aerosoles and our trusted service providers use cookies and pixel tags on our website and in our marketing emails to: help us recognize you when you arrive at our website; keep track of your order and preferences as you shop; analyze the performance of our advertising, promotions, marketing emails, the features of our website; or to deliver content in a format that your browser supports. We may also use cookies and pixel tags to personalize your shopping experience, speed your checkout process and improve the content of our website and emails. In addition, we may use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.aerosoles.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=61672&cname=Aerosoles&cmagic=dede3d&clogo=61672.png&loc=us&lang=en-us)

Cookies are small, removable data files stored by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. However, since cookies are used to remember the items you add to your shopping bag, if you choose to not accept cookies you will not be able to complete an order on our website. 

Pixel tags, also know as clear GIFs or web beacons, are non-visible image tags containing computer code that are placed on the pages of our website and in our emails but are not stored on your computer. When used in conjunction with cookies, pixel tags generate a notice to us when a particular page or email is accessed. If you choose to not accept cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous visitor.

Information We Share with Others

Service Providers: We provide information to trusted service providers that we contract to perform services, such as processing credit cards, checks, orders, returns, refunds and credits; completing our catalog and promotional mailings, transmitting emails from us to you and managing customer information. These companies are not authorized to use this information in any other manner. 

Third-Party Offers: Occasionally we make our postal mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products or services may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such mailings, just contact us. We do NOT share email addresses or telephone numbers for any third-party offers. 

Online Behavioral Advertising: We may share anonymous versions of user information collected at this site. We may use that information to link to and issue anonymous cookies containing demographic or intent-based data for online behavioral advertising purposes. Such cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. If you would like to opt out of online behavioral advertising from our third party service providers, you may do so here: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. 

Aggregate Information: We share the aggregate, statistical information about our site and customers with other outside companies that we contract with to help us manage or measure the performance of our site, our advertising, promotions, and identify which pages, products, offers, website features and services our customers and visitors prefer. This aggregated information does not include individual names or any personally identifiable data. 

Others: On rare occasions, we may be required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. Also, if the ownership of all or a part of a business within the Aerosoles were to change, customer information pertinent to that business’s operations would likely be transferred to, or licensed for use by, the new owner.

Your Choices Regarding the Use of the Information We Collect

If you prefer that we do not share personal information about you with any of the companies outside Aerosoles that we have authorized to send you promotional information about their products or services just contact us.

Email Communications

From time to time, we may notify you of Aerosoles promotions, announcements or events via email. However, we do NOT sell or rent your email address to others. You may unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any promotional email you receive from us. You may also call, email or write us as detailed above.

Safeguarding the Information We Collect

When you complete a transaction at Aerosoles.com, we use Transfer Layer Security (TLS), which is authenticated by GeoTrust, an independent agency, to encrypt your credit card information, before it travels over the Internet to our secure servers. TLS technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. 

Certain browsers will not allow communication through secure servers. If this is the case, you won't be able to place an order online. If you have any problems placing an order online contact us as detailed above. 

Within Aerosoles, we have appropriate security measures in place to protect against unauthorized disclosures of your personal information. We limit the information we provide to outside companies to only the information we believe is appropriate to enable them to carry out their responsibilities.

Updating Your Aerosoles Contact Information

You can update or correct your name, address, telephone number, or email address by writing to us at Aerosoles Direct Division, PO Box 1916, Edison, NJ 08818-1916, calling us at [800-798-9478](tel:1-800-798-9478) or email us.

Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly sell or ship any items ordered through website directly to anyone we know to be under the age of 18 nor do we collect personal information from anyone we know to be under the age of 18. Our website is intended to be used by adults only. Children should only access and use this website with the supervision of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us.

Links to Other Sites

While visiting Aerosoles.com, you may link to websites operated by our business partners, service providers or other third parties. When you provide personal information at one of those websites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that website, not the Aerosoles Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read that policy before submitting any personal information.

Privacy Policy Effective Date

This policy is in effect each time you visit our site. Please check our Privacy Policy each time you visit as should our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website. If you are concerned with how your information is used you should check our Privacy Policy each time before submitting any information.
